So the communication management plan,
as I already mentioned, when you plan
communications, and every time you plan,
you at least produce a plan.
So the communication management plan,
again, think journalism documents,
who needs what, when, where, why,
how.
It will include the
communication requirements,
what people are saying
they need when they need it.
in the right format that they need it.
All right.
When we will communicate?
When will information be updated?
Especially if we're using SharePoint,
a repository.
When will information be updated and
available?
Escalation processes for issues and
unresolved items.
So there is a team charter that,
of course, with our team members,
how they're supposed to communicate with
each other.
And it also says how to make decisions,
how they will resolve conflict.
But communication management plan is
overall, if we, with any of our
stakeholders, are not
able to actually resolve
a conflict because we should be able to.
But if not, we'll go back to our
communication.
management plan to
figure out what the chain
of command is, the escalation process is.
But these are things we should always try
to resolve first.
Any constraints we know
of to communications, you
might have people out in
the middle of the desert.
All right, meeting best practices.
And who's responsible for communicating?
It's not always the PM.
There are other team members who will be
communicating.
So we're stating who will be doing what.